Contact

hunter@bakerycos.com

www.linkedin.com/in/ ryanhunterwilkinson (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Supply Chain

Database Administration

Strategic Planning

Ryan Hunter Wilkinson

Director | Enterprise Technology at The Bakery Cos Nashville, Tennessee

Summary

Experienced Director Of Technology with a demonstrated history of working in the food production industry. Skilled in Sage X3 ERP, Database Management, SQL, Food Manufacturing, Operations Management, and Warehouse Operations. Strong information technology professional with a Bachelor of Arts (BA) focused in Business Administration and Management, from Belmont University.

Experience

The Bakery Cos. 14 years 9 months

Director | Enterprise Technology September 2016 - Present (3 years 8 months) Greater Nashville Area, TN

Plant Manager

March 2016 - September 2016 (7 months)

Cornerstone Frozen Bakery Products | Cold Storage of Nashville

Director of Operations - Frozen Division December 2014 - February 2016 (1 year 3 months)

Greater Nashville Area

General Manager

January 2009 - December 2014 (6 years)

Cold Storage of Nashville

Supply Chain Manager

January 2009 - December 2014 (6 years)

Cold Storage of Nashville

Warehouse Associate

August 2005 - January 2009 (3 years 6 months)

Cold Storage of Nashville

Creative Occasions
Warehouse Associate
September 2004 - July 2005 (11 months)

The Bakery Cos.

Production

August 2002 - August 2004 (2 years 1 month)

Nashville Bun Company

Education

Belmont University
Bachelor of Arts (BA), Business Administration and Management,
General · (2008 - 2014)

University of Mississippi (2001 - 2002)